
export const data= [
{
    question : "Who is the father of Computers?",
    option1 : "James Gosling",
    option2 : "Charles Babbage",
    option3 : "Dennis Ritchie",
    option4 : "Bjarne Stroustrup",
    Answer: 2,
},
{
    question : "Which of the following is the correct abbreviation of COMPUTER?",
    option1 : "Commonly Occupied Machines Used in Technical and Educational Research",
    option2 : "Commonly Operated Machines Used in Technical and Environmental Research",
    option3 : "Commonly Oriented Machines Used in Technical and Educational Research",
    option4 : "Commonly Operated Machines Used in Technical and Educational Research",
    Answer: 4,
},
{
    question : "What is the full form of CPU?",
    option1 : " Computer Processing Unit",
    option2 : "Computer Principle Unit",
    option3 : " Central Processing Unit",
    option4 : "Control Processing Unit",
    Answer: 3,
},
{
    question : "Which of the following computer language is written in binary codes only?",
    option1 : "pascal ",
    option2 : "machine language",
    option3 : " C",
    option4 : "C#",
    Answer: 2,
},
{
    question : "Which of the following is the brain of the computer?",
    option1 : "Central Processing Unit",
    option2 : "Memory",
    option3 : " Arithmetic and Logic unit",
    option4 : " Control unit",
    Answer: 1,
},
{
    question : "Which of the following is not a characteristic of a computer?",
    option1 : " Versatility",
    option2 : "Accuracy",
    option3 : " Diligence",
    option4 : "I.Q.",
    Answer: 4,
},
{
    question : " Which of the following is the smallest unit of data in a computer?",
    option1 : " Bit",
    option2 : "KB",
    option3 : " Nibble",
    option4 : "Byte",
    Answer: 1,
},
{
    question : " Which of the following monitor looks like a television and are normally used with non-portable computer systems?",
    option1 : "LED ",
    option2 : "LCD",
    option3 : "CRT ",
    option4 : "Flat Panel Monitors",
    Answer: 3,
},
{
    question : " Which of the following is not a type of computer code?",
    option1 : " EDIC",
    option2 : "ASCII",
    option3 : "BCD ",
    option4 : "EBCDIC",
    Answer: 1,
},
{
    question : "Which of the following part of a processor contains the hardware necessary to perform all the operations required by a computer?",
    option1 : "Controller ",
    option2 : "Registers",
    option3 : "Cache ",
    option4 : " Data path",
    Answer: 4,
},



]
export default data;